Laura Antunez

Augusta, GA | 305-764-6528 | https://lauraantunez024.github.io/portfolio $_2$.1/ lauraantunez024@gmail.com | https://www.linkedin.com/in/laura-antunez/ | https://github.com/lauraantunez024

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Motivated Junior Quality Assurance Engineer with a strong passion for software development. Self motivated, I transitioned from journalism to being the sole QA of the integrations team. When I'm not working in QA, I'm working on a software project or principle with the goal of continuously improving my ability to test and understand software. Also great at collaborating and communicating new ideas.

- Solid foundation in User Experience Design with React and Vue frameworks.
- Experience in RESTful API development and testing using Node.js or Ruby on Rails.
- Over 2 year experience working remotely in tech for a SAAS company.

CERTIFICATIONS

CodecademyHTML/CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap, JQueryJuly 2021CodecademyData Analyst Career PathApril 2021AWS Skill BuilderCloud PractitionerIn progress

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages: Javascript, Python, Ruby, SQL (Postgres, Redis), NoSQL (MongoDB), HTML, JSON, CSS, Spanish

Frameworks: MVC, MEVN/MERN, jQuery, React, Vue, Next, Node, Ruby on Rails, ExpressJS, Bootstrap, RESTAPI, Sequelize

DevOps and API Tools: Git, Docker, Swagger, Postman **Cloud and Security Tools**: AWS, Heroku, Linux, Vercel

Others: Data analysis (Hypothesis testing, data manipulation, data viz), Agile (Scrum), Debugging, Jira, ClickUP

EXPERIENCE

Quality Assurance Engineer | SpringBig

August 2021 -Present

- Sole QA for integrations and payment team that responsibilities included building a robust subscription program from the ground up
- Used AWS Elastic beanstalk to test the environment using the rails console, including manipulating date time and simulating services that would otherwise take hours or days to test manually.
- Used white and gray box testing for a variety of features, hot fixes and epics, including for integration features.
- Learned and used debugging techniques when testing back end features to better describe root cause of the issue.

Quality Assurance Intern | *SpringBig*

March 2022 – June 2022

- Performed regression testing to ensure that existing functionality was not impacted by new features or bug fixes.
- Actively participated in daily stand-up meetings to discuss task progress and projects, including being one of two QAs to represent the integrations team.
- Conducted manual testing of UI and UX features for multiple applications as well as created Postman collections for automated api test cases.
- Identified, documented, tracked, and reported defects in the software development lifecycle. Worked closely with developers to understand feature requirements.

Data Product and Design Intern | Hechinger Report

June 2021 – August 2021

- Utilized D3.js to create data visualizations for a self-pitched and written article.
- Collaborated with journalists to extract and utilize data from large datasets for stories using Python pandas and NumPy.

EDUCATION

Florida International University | Bachelor of Arts in Journal **Georgia Tech** | Full Stack Development Bootcamp

December 2020 August 2022

PROJECTS

Hechinger Report Sex Ed Article | HTML/CSS, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, D3.js

September 2021

- Researched and using data analysis practices to write an article about the limits of sexual education in the US.
- Created an interactive map using HTML/CSS, Javascript, Bootstrap and JQuery.
- Had a D3. js data visualization showing the different kinds of sexual education programs each state had.

Mobile Friendly Portfolio | React/Next.js, Node.js, Twilio

in progress

- Mobile friendly website that includes home page, portfolio subdirectory with pages pointing to different projects
- Includes contact form that uses Twilio to send a text message to the user with the contact form submission

Time Garden | *Node.js, Express, Mongoose*

in progress

- Conceptualized idea from scratch and building it solo using MEVN stack
- Time management app that uses seeds as to do list items that are planted into a schedule and bloom when the task is completed.